

CONTACT ME AT

- cyaco33@gmail.com
- in carlos yaco tincusi
- @yacodev
- https://carlosyaco.com

SKILLS SUMMARY

Javascript

- React.js
- 底 Node.js
- Ruby
- Rails
- HTML HTML
- CSS/SASS
 - MySQL
- PostgresSQL
- MongoDB
- Github

CARLOS YACO

FULL STACK DEVELOPER - ELECTRONIC ENGINEER

PERSONAL PROFILE

I'm a full-Stack Developer in love with technology who enjoys solving problems using software. I have two years of experience leading and working with teams to develop software for the construction sector, and in this period I founded my own startup (Construtec). Before I worked as a project manager in the construction sector, I worked for the Peruvian government building tracks, schools, and hospitals. I enjoy reading books about technology companies and everything related to entrepreneurship. I look forward to applying my leadership skills to help solve global problems in the technology industry.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front-end Developer.

Regional Management of Housing, Construction and Sanitation | August 2020 - December 2020

- Designed and implemented a web application with **React** to give training to personnel on a regional level.
- Led the engineering team to develop web application (http://lacasadelatm.com)

CEO - Web Developer.

Construtec Perú | July 2019 - July 2020

- Developed the website (www.constructecperu.com).
- Designed an executive business model to fill a market need, and then marketed and released the product.
- Led three engineers through the process of developing the software CPIP (Control of Public Investment Project).
- Gave training to new users who bought the software.

Product owner.

Smart Cities Perúl Octuber 2019 - December 2019

- Led the engineering team to develop software to monitor the status of the construction process of the projects by the regional government of Cusco.
- Designed the UX and UI of the web platform.
- Gave training to civil engineers of the regional government of Cusco.

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

Codeable (www.codeable.la)

Full Stack Developer | Lima -Perú | 2021

Polytechnic University of Valencia

Master's in Project Management and Planning in Civil Engineering | Valencia - Spain | 2017 - 2018

National University San Antonio Abad of Cusco

Electronic Engineer | Cusco - Perú | 2003 - 2008